美…好…的…早晨又来到
Morning's here The morning's here
阳光露脸，晴空万里
Sunshine is here The sky is clear The morning's here
美好的早晨又来到
The morning's here
你一定要唱吗？今天是星期六
Do you have to do that? It's Saturday!
别这样嘛，早晨来到了
Oh,come on!Morning's here!
我恨这层公寓
I hate this apartment!
我恨墙壁的颜色 我恨这里还是有鸡鸭的味道
I hate this wall color! I hate that it still smells like bird!
我恨那个唱歌的人
I hate that singing guy!
不会吧，我好喜欢他
Are you kidding? I love that guy!
美好的早晨又来到…
Morning's here
闭嘴
Stop it!
小心我宰了你
I will kill you.
我恨我的房间那么小
I hate that my room is so small.
我就觉得空间够用，学学我吧
I have all the space I need. Do what I did.
你连床都没有 睡在地板上
You don't even have a bed. You sleep in a ball on the floor!
你别再唠叨了 我很努力的把这里布置舒适
I am tired of your bellyaching.I've worked hard to make this a nice place for us.
我知道，对不起 没关系
I know. I'm so sorry.I'm sorry,okay?
看吧，这里很好
It's a great apartment!
闭嘴，这里烂死了
Shut up! This place is a hole!
本集播出：“闪电决定”
The One with All the Haste
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
我还是不敢相信你穿了耳洞
I still can't believe you've got an earring!
我知道 我是谁？大卫鲍伊（电影演员）？
I know,I know. Who am l? David Bowie?
他会那样吗？
He does that?
不晓得，随便
I don't know. Whatever.
你这样看起来好危险
I think it makes you look really dangerous.
我知道
Oh,I know.
你知道吗？
You know what?
要不是你，我永远不会穿耳洞
I never would've gotten this if it weren't for you.
真的，跟你在一起时
When I'm with you,I'm like...
我就变了一个人
this whole other guy.
我爱那个人
I love that guy!
我也很爱你
I mean,I love you too. A lot.
不过那个人…我爱那个人
But that guy!I love that guy
我爱你们两个
I love both of you.
我好不想走
I wish I didn't have to go.
那就别走，
Then don't.
留下来 别急着回伦敦，再留1天就好
Stay here. Don't go so soon to London.Just one more day.
罗斯，别再引诱我了
Please don't do this to me again.
我也想 但我请了那么多假，会被开除
I'd stay,but I've already missed so much work. They'll fire me.
那你就可以尽情留下来了
So? Then you could stay as long as you want.
我也很想
I wish I could.
不要，不要打包，拜托啦
Oh,no. Don't start packing.Come on!
我想你不懂什么叫打包
I don't think you understand packing.
我不想拖到最后一刻 上次我把球鞋忘在这里
I don't want to leave it till last. Last time,I left my knickers here.
我知道，我有偷穿
Yeah,I know. I tried them on.
不会吧
You didn't!
骗你的，我不想学另一个我
No,I didn't. I didn't want to be "that guy."
什么？ 你的裤子
Excuse me?Your pants.
喔对，你喜欢吗？
Oh yeah! You like them?
我去二手衣店买孕妇装
I went to a used-clothes store and got maternity stuff.
这条裤子好舒服
These are so comfortable.
菲比，那是圣诞裤
Pheebs,those are Santa pants.
什么？ 圣诞裤
Santa pants.
圣诞老人的裤子
Santa Claus' pants.
才不是，这是孕妇裤
No. They're maternity pants.
你看，还附赠宝宝姓名表
They even came with a list of baby names. See?
这些名字好，这些名字不好
These names are good,and these are bad.
菲比，驯鹿都好吗？
Hey,Phoebes.So,how are the elves?
我不知道，那你…那个…
I don't know. How are the...you know?
你的衣服不好玩
Your clothes aren't funny.
我该穿什么去看尼克队比赛？
What should I wear to a Knicks game?
上面印有 “我不看篮球”的衣服？
A T-shirt that says,"l Don't Belong Here"?
你们有票？
You have tickets?
妈离婚时分到爸的季票 就送给我了
Mom got Dad's season tickets in the divorce,so she gave them to me.
位子显然很好
Apparently,they're good seats.
天哪，几乎就在场边 我可以把履历表塞给伍迪艾伦（著名导演）
Oh,my God! Those are almost on the floor!I could slip Woody Allen my resume.
你们想要吗？
Do you guys want these?
废话
Yeah,we do!
那就给你们 谢谢
Well,you got them!
只要把这里还给我们
Just give us our apartment back.
想不到有这一招
Oh,I didn't see that coming.
你是说真的？
Are you serious?
我们知道这些票的价值
Come on. We know what these are worth.
你们以为我们是白痴吗？
Do you think we're stupid?
不是白痴，是很恶劣
Not stupid. You're meaner than I thought.
如何？
What do you say?
想都别想，我才不会为了球票 放弃我的单身公寓
Forget it. I'm not giving up my bachelor pad for basketball seats.
你的单身公寓？ 你带女生回来过吗？
Your "bachelor pad"?Have you even had a girl here?
没有
No.
但是乔伊有 我早上都会跟她们聊天
But Joey has,and I usually talk to them in the morning.
没错
Yeah,you do!
拜托啦
Come on!
甘瑟，请给我两杯卡布奇诺
Gunther,can I get two cups of chino,please?
很有趣
Good one.
季票耶！你知道那代表什么？
Come on. Season tickets!Season tickets! You know what that means?
别想了，我绝不让出那层公寓
I'm not giving up the apartment.
小时候我爸的公司都会送季票 给业绩第一的业务员
When I was a kid,my dad's company gave season tickets...
我爸从来没拿到过
...to the No. 1 salesman every year. My dad never won.
不过他也不在业务部 但我还是一直耿耿于怀
Of course,he wasn't in sales. But still,I never forgot that!
你们在啊
Hey guys!
天哪
Oh,my God!
我们笑你笑得还不够吗？
We don't make enough fun of you already?
艾蜜莉说服我去穿的
Oh,yeah. Emily convinced me to do it.
你知道威猛乐队解散了吧？
You do know that Wham broke up?
我喜欢，艾蜜莉喜欢 这样最重要
I like it. Emily likes it. That's what counts.
你们好吗？
So,how are you guys doing?
别戴了耳环还装正常
Don't try and talk all normal with that thing in your ear.
艾蜜莉呢？ 去跟她舅舅道别
Where's Emily?She's saying goodbye to her uncle.
她不是才刚来？ 就是嘛
Didn't she,like,just get here?
别激动，老虎
Easy,tiger.
我好讨厌这样
I just hate this so much.
每次去机场接她，我都好开心
Every time I go pick her up at the airport,it's so great.
但是我又会想 “过两天又要送她来机场了”
But I'm thinking,"I'll be right back in a couple of days,dropping her off."
那你要怎么办？ 不怎么办
-So what'll you do? -There's nothing to do.
她住在那里，我住在这里 她得搬来这里
She lives there. I live here.She'd have to move here.
她应该搬来这里
She should move here.
什么？ 我可以叫她跟我住
What?-I can ask her to live with me.
你说真的吗？ 为什么不行？
-Are you serious?-I mean,why not?
你才认识她6星期
-You've only known her six weeks!
我冰箱里有盒牛奶放得还更久
I've got a carton of milk in my fridge I've had a longer relationship with.
我跟她在一起时 她会激发出我好的一面
Look,guys,when I'm with her,it's like....She brings out this great side of me.
我爱她
I mean,I love her,you know?
我也爱那盒牛奶
And I love the milk!
但我不会要一个英国女生 跟我同居
But I won't ask some British girl to move in with me.
乔伊，该你说了
Joey,you say things now.
罗斯，他说得对，艾蜜莉很棒 她很棒
Look,Ross. He's right. Emily's great.She's great!
但这样太快了，你只会吓到她
But this is too soon. You'll only scare her.
我不想吓到她 没错，别坏了好事，别太心急
I don't want to do that.You don't want to wreck it. Don't go too fast.
你们说得对，我不会这样
No. You're right. I know,you're right.I'm not going to do it.
谢了，两位
-Thanks guys. -No problem.
记得临走时摇它两下 （威猛乐队的歌词）
Just remember to wake us up before you go-go.
太难了，太难了
It's too hard. Too hard!
两位，最后的机会
All right. Last chance for the tickets.
否则我就送给我的新男友 约书亚
Otherwise,I give them to my new boyfriend,Joshua.
不用了
No,thank you.
等一下…拜托，跟她们换啦
Wait,wait. Come on,come on! Let's trade.
时机正好，我刚把马桶堵住
The timing's perfect! I just clogged the toilet!
我跟你一样想要球票 但住过这里就觉得对面太小了
I want those seats. But we can't live in the small apartment...after living here!
你看过《献给阿尔杰农的花》这本书没有？
Ever read Flowers for Algernon?
有 你看过《运动画报》吗？
Ever read Sports Illustrated?
我没看过你说的
No,I didn't read yours!
我们晚上就可以去看球
We can go to the game tonight!
她们提出比季票更好的东西 我才要考虑
The only way I'll consider this is...if they offer more than just season seats.
是尼克队耶 去他的尼克队
-It's the Knicks! -Screw the Knicks!
我不是那个意思 我是说这层公寓的价值要更大
I didn't mean that. I just meant that..the apartment is worth so much more..
尼克队万岁 对，尼克队万岁
And the Knicks rule.Yeah,the Knicks rule!
怎样？要不要？
So? Are you going to do it?
不要，因为这个交易不公平
No,we're not going to because it's not an even trade.
好，听着
All right,look.
要是你们能保住公寓 又拿到球票呢？
What if you could keep the apartment and the tickets?
成交
Done!
让我说完，我是说我们来赌 赢的人通杀
Let me finish. I'm talking about a bet. Winner takes all.
我们可能输光光 或是通杀
We could get nothing.Or everything.
我喜欢
I like that.
怎么样？ 不要
What do you say?
赌了啦
Just do it!
真有说服力啊
Oh! I'm convinced!
拜托啦，我也会为你这么做
Come on,man! You know I'd do it for you.
因为你是我最好的朋友
Because you're my best friend.
好吧 但你1整年不准再用这招
All right. But you can't use that again for a whole year.
我赌了
I'm in.
好兴奋喔，你们要赌什么？
This is so exciting! What are you going to bet?
就让菲比决定
We should let Phoebe decide...
因为只有她没有利害关系 而且她好美
...because she's the only one who's impartial,and she's so pretty.
我知道了
I have a game!
很棒喔 比什么？
-This is great! -What's the game?
没有名字 不，叫菲比球
It doesn't have a name. No,okay. Phoebe Ball!
不，没有名字
No,it doesn't have a name.
莫妮卡 你最喜欢树的哪一点？
What is your favorite thing about trees?
树是绿色的 很好，5分
-They're green? -Good! Five points!
乔伊，同样的问题
Same question.
树很高 3分
-They're tall. -Three points!
都答得很好 但我们说的是阔叶植物
Both fine answers,but we were looking for leafy. Leafy.
这根本不是比赛
That's not even a game.
闭嘴，我们领先
Shut up. We're winning!
你们想速战速决？我们抽牌 点数大的赢，如何？
You want to finish this? We get a deck of cardsHigh card wins. What do you say?.
好，就这么办 我刚好有牌
-Let's do it! -Oh,I have cards!
在这里
Yeah. Here.
这是魔术牌
No,these are the trick deck.
这一副
Here,yes.
好，你们先抽
Okay,you guys pick first.
4点 够少了
-Four. -That's a low one!
菲比，你看，我不敢看
You look. I can't do it.
为什么我就敢看？
What makes you think I can?
A
Ace!
你们在爽什么？ 我们把这里抢回来了
Why are you hugging?We won our apartment back!
什么？A最大 J Q K A
What? Ace is high! Jack,queen,king,ace!
不对，A最小，A234
No! Ace is low! Ace,two,three,four!
我不知道
I don't know.
你们看
Look it!
再抽一次
Come on,pick again!
我要公寓，我要公寓
Come on,apartment! Come on,apartment!
Q点数很大
I know queen is high!
但是大不过…
Not as high as....
成功了！K
It worked! King!
再抽一次
We pick again! We pick again!
为什么？ 我不知道
-Why? -I don't know.
球票请拿来
Tickets,please.
场边区喔
Courtside,baby!
很精彩的比赛
Seriously,good game,though. Good game.
她们气什么气？ 公寓都还给她们了
What are they so mad about? They got the apartment back.
没有啦
No,they didn't.
趁你不在打包好了
Packed while you were gone.
我留了双球鞋在枕头底下
I left knickers under your pillow.
搬来跟我住
Move in with me?
什么？
What?
别怕，我知道听起来很疯狂 别人会说太快了
Don't be scared. It sounds crazy,and people will say it's too soon...
但是你想想，那样多棒啊
...but just think. Think how great it would be.
我不知道
I don't know.
要我离开伦敦…
Leaving London....
我的家人都在那里 我知道
My whole family lives there....
我的工作 你可以在这里找工作
-My job. -You'll get a job here.
我常听说美国人的工作 都被外国人抢走了
I always hear about them foreigners stealing American jobs.
你也可以
That could be you.
但事关我的人生
Yeah,but it's my whole life.
你来英国
You come to England.
我不行，我很愿意
I would. I really would.
但我儿子在这里 我离不开他 没别的办法了吗？
But my son is here.I can't leave him. You don't think there's any way?
我看是没有了
I don't think so.
如果是长久的打算就不同了
It would be different if it was way into the future...
例如结婚什么的 什么？
...and we were getting married.What?
好，我不该提结婚的 别被我吓到
Right. I shouldn't have said "married." Please don't go freaky on me.
我不是认真的 我没说，我收回
I didn't mean it. I take it back.
不，不要收回
No. Don't.
何不就这么做？
Why don't we?
做什么？
Why don't we what?
结婚啊
Get married.
你疯了
You are mad!
我没有，这样很完美 比你搬来住更棒
No,I'm not! It's perfect. It's better than you moving here.
我们可以永远在一起 我就是要这样
It's us together forever,and that's what I want.
我们才认识6星期 我知道，那又怎样？
-We've known each other six weeks! -I know.
谁说不行？这样就不行吗？
So what? Who's to say? Does that mean we can't do it?
听着，我跟卡萝结婚前 在一起4年
Look. I was with Carol for four years before we got married...
最后跟一个怀孕的女同志离婚
...and I wound up divorced from a pregnant lesbian.
这么做…对我们是顺理成章
I mean,this....This makes sense for us.
我们第一次约会 就跑去佛罗蒙特度周末
Our first date,we ended up spending the whole weekend in Vermont.
昨晚我还去穿耳洞，我耶
I mean,last night I got my ear pierced. Me!
这个感觉很对，不是吗？
This feels right.Doesn't it?
我爸妈会气死
My parents will be really mad.
你答应了吗？那是好吗？
Are you saying,"Yes"? Is that "Yes"?Yes.
我们要结婚了 天哪
-We're getting married! -Oh,my God!
我们要结婚了，天哪
We're getting married!
过来
Come here,come here.
艾蜜莉，你愿意嫁给我吗？
Emily,will you marry me?
愿意
Yes
有一点小
It's a bit small.
真是的，我还以为会很浪漫
Damn! I thought that'd be romantic as hell.
是很浪漫
It was.
真是史上最棒的位子
Those were,like,the best seats ever!
要不要把衣服送给女生 表示和解？
Should we give these to the girls? Like a peace offering?
好主意，反正不用钱又太小
That's very nice. Plus,they were free and too small.
天哪
Oh,God!
你要喝酒吗？
Hey,you want a beer?
我知道
I know!
开门！开门
Open up! Open up! Open up!
明天早上再说
We'll discuss it in the morning.
这是怎么回事？
What the hell is going on?
我们把我们家抢回来了
We took our apartment back!
跟我无关
I had nothing to do with it.
好吧，是我的主意 但我并不好过
Okay,it was my idea. But I don't feel good about it.
我们现在就换回来
We are switching back right now.
不要，我们不走
No,we're not. We're not leaving!
你们非走不可，你们都有工作
You'll have to. You both have jobs.
等你们去上班，我们就换回来
As soon as you do,we'll switch back!
你们阻止不了的 对吧，乔伊？
- You can't stop us.Right,Joe?
我不晓得
-I don't know.
什么？
What?
我不想再搬了
I don't want to move again,with....
我不管，这是我们的公寓 她们偷了…
This is our apartment and they stole
你们偷了！
You stole!
我们的公寓 我们光明正大的赢了两次
Our apartment! We won it fair and square. Twice!
我现在就要要回来 我现在就要要回来
And I am getting it back right now! I'm getting it back right now!
好，我们早料到会有这种反应
All right.We figured you might respond this way,
所以我们准备了备案
so we have a backup offer.
不要，你们搞不定我们的
No more offers. You can't offer anything to us!
让我们留在这里 为了表示感谢
-Let us keep the apartment and -As a thank you...
瑞秋和我会接吻1分钟
...Rachel and I will kiss for one minute.
完全值得 好爽的1分钟
-Totally worth it! -That was one good minute!
晚安 晚安
Good night.
男人真是白痴 就是啊
-Men are such idiots. -I know.
那么白痴的事 居然让我们得逞了
Can you believe something that stupid actually got us our apartment back?
要是你们上次比完就这么做 谁都不必搬家
If you had just done that after the last contest...no one would have had to move at all.
就装做没这回事
Let's pretend that's not true.
围巾织好了
Scarf's done.
快点 好
Come on,come on!
怎么了？ 罗斯有大事要宣布
What's going on?Ross has some big thing to tell everyone.
艾蜜莉和我决定…要结婚
Emily and l,we decided...to get married.
什么？
What?
你也怀孕了？
Oh,are you pregnant too?
没有
No.
什么…怎么…
When did How did you
我们就是决定要结婚
We just decided to go for it.
这个决定是仓促了些，但是… 感觉真的很对
We know it's a bit hasty...but it just feels so right.
我正在告诉他们… 我听到了
I was just telling the guys Yeah,I heard.
太好了
I think it's great!
我真替你高兴
I'm so happy for you!
是啊，恭喜
Well,yeah! Congratulations!
你居然要结婚了 是啊
I can't believe you're getting married!
莫妮卡和瑞秋亲热
Monica and Rachel made out.
美…好…的…早晨又来到
Morning's here The morning's here
阳光露脸，晴空万里
Sunshine is here The sky is clear
美好的早晨
The morning's here
你回来了 准备就绪
-Hey,you're back! -Hey,get into gear
早餐就快上桌 夜晚的黑暗一扫而空
Breakfast is near The dark of night has disappeared
我们明天见 好
I'll see you tomorrow morning!